{
  "array2DQuiz" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "7.9",
    "option1" : "7.3",
    "option2" : "9.2",
    "option3" : "7.9",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is in values[2][1]?\ndouble[][] my2DArray = {{1.2, 9.0, 3.2},{9.2, 0.5, 1.5, -1.2},{7.3, 7.9, 4.8}};"
  }, {
    "answer" : "my2DArray = new Double[5][7];",
    "option1" : "my2DArray = new stuff[5][7];",
    "option2" : "my2DArray = new Double[5][7];",
    "option3" : "my2DArray = double[5][7];",
    "option4" : "my2DArray = double[7][5];",
    "question" : "Given, double[][] my2DArray;\nHow to we construct an array with 5 rows and 7 columns?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "int[][] array = new int[7][];",
    "option1" : "int[][] array = new int[7][];",
    "option2" : "int[][] array = new int[7];",
    "option3" : "int[][] array = new int[][7];",
    "option4" : "int[] array[7] = new int[];",
    "question" : "How do we construct a 2D array with 7 rows but no columns"
  }, {
    "answer" : "2D Arrays are used to create data in two dimensions",
    "option1" : "2D Arrays are used to create data in three dimensions",
    "option2" : "2D Arrays are used to create two arrays at once",
    "option3" : "2D Arrays are used to create an array with only two elements",
    "option4" : "2D Arrays are used to create data in two dimensions",
    "question" : "What are 2D Arrays?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "9.0",
    "option1" : "1.2",
    "option2" : "9.2",
    "option3" : "0.5",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is in values[0][1]?\ndouble[][] my2DArray = {{1.2, 9.0, 3.2},{9.2, 0.5, 1.5, -1.2},{7.3, 7.9, 4.8}};"
  } ],
  "array2DRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "while loop, for loop, do...while loop",
    "option1" : "count up loop, count down loop, infinite loop",
    "option2" : "infinite loop, counting loop, nested loop",
    "option3" : "while loop, for loop, do...while loop",
    "option4" : "counting loop,  sentinel-controlled loop,  and result-controlled loop",
    "question" : "What are the three general types of looping structures?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "One more time than the inner loop",
    "option1" : "Forever",
    "option2" : "One fewer time than the inner loop",
    "option3" : "Each time the inner loop is run",
    "option4" : "One more time than the inner loop",
    "question" : "How often is the outer loop of a nested loop run?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "5",
    "option1" : "0",
    "option2" : "5",
    "option3" : "6",
    "option4" : "4",
    "question" : "What is the length of the array?\n{59, 1, 67, 472, 982}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "True",
    "option1" : "False",
    "option2" : "Error",
    "option3" : "True",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nint a=110,b=25,c=310,d=415;\nif(d>a)&&(a<b){\n    System.out.println(\"True\");\n}else{\n    System.out.println(\"False\");\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "None of the above",
    "option1" : "s1",
    "option2" : "42.0",
    "option3" : "42",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is the result of the follwoing?\nString s1 = new String(\"42\");\ndouble a = Integer.parseDouble(s1);"
  } ],
  "arrayQuiz" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "6",
    "option1" : "9",
    "option2" : "12",
    "option3" : "6",
    "option4" : "8",
    "question" : "What is the value at position 4 in the array?\n{9, 4, 12, 2, 6, 8, 18}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "7",
    "option1" : "0",
    "option2" : "5",
    "option3" : "6",
    "option4" : "7",
    "question" : "What is the length of the array?\n{9, 4, 12, 2, 6, 8, 18}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "String[] months = new String[12];",
    "option1" : "String[] months = new String[12];",
    "option2" : "String months = new String[12];",
    "option3" : "String[] months = new String[];",
    "option4" : "String[12] months = new String[];",
    "question" : "How do we create an array of 12 strings called months?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "It is a container that holds a constant fixed number of same value types",
    "option1" : "It is a container that holds a constant fixed number of different value types",
    "option2" : "It is a container that holds a constant fixed number of same value types",
    "option3" : "It is a container that holds a number of same value types",
    "option4" : "It is a container that holds a constant fixed number of same similar value types",
    "question" : "What is an array?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "2345",
    "option1" : "12345",
    "option2" : "1234",
    "option3" : "01234",
    "option4" : "2345",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nint myArray[] = {1, 2, 3, 4, 5};\nfor(int i = 1; i < myArray.length; i++){\n    System.out.print(myArray[i]);\n}"
  } ],
  "arrayRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "0.0",
    "option1" : "0",
    "option2" : "0.0",
    "option3" : "null",
    "option4" : "1.0",
    "question" : "What is the default value of a double?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "ooth University",
    "option1" : "nooth University",
    "option2" : "Maynooth University",
    "option3" : "oth University",
    "option4" : "ooth University",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nString s1 = new String(\"Maynooth University\");\ns1.substring(4);"
  }, {
    "answer" : "11",
    "option1" : "11",
    "option2" : "9",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "10",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nint a = 10;\nif(a == 10){\n    a++;\n}else{\n    a--;\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "False",
    "option1" : "True",
    "option2" : "Error",
    "option3" : "False",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nint a=30;\nif(a == 40){\n    System.out.println(\"True\");\n}else{\n    System.out.println(\"False\");\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "True",
    "option1" : "True",
    "option2" : "False",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is the result of the follwoing?\nString s1 = new String(\"Maynooth\");\nString s1 = new String(\"maynooth\");\ns1.equalsignoresCase(s2);"
  } ],
  "booQuiz" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "true",
    "option1" : "true",
    "option2" : "false",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is the output of the following?\nint a = 14; b= 4;\nboolean x = (a>b)?true:false;"
  }, {
    "answer" : "It is used to produce a true or false value",
    "option1" : "It is used to produce a false value",
    "option2" : "It is used to produce a true value",
    "option3" : "It is used to produce a true or false value",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What are boolean expressions?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "None of the above",
    "option1" : "False",
    "option2" : "Error",
    "option3" : "true",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nint a=0,b=5,c=10,d=15;\nif(d>a)&&(a<b){\n    System.out.println(\"True\");\n}else{\n    System.out.println(\"False\");\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "True",
    "option1" : "False",
    "option2" : "True",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nint a=0,b=5,c=10,d=15;\nif(d>a)||(a>b){\n    System.out.println(\"True\");\n}else{\n    System.out.println(\"False\");\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "True",
    "option1" : "True",
    "option2" : "Error",
    "option3" : "False",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nint a=30;\nif(a != 40){\n    System.out.println(\"True\");\n}else{\n    System.out.println(\"False\");\n}"
  } ],
  "booRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "true",
    "option1" : "0",
    "option2" : "true",
    "option3" : "false",
    "option4" : "-3",
    "question" : "Which is the result of the following?\nString s1 = new String(\"abc\");\nString s2 = new String(\"def\");\nSystem.out.println(s1.equals(s2));"
  }, {
    "answer" : "\"0\"",
    "option1" : "0",
    "option2" : "\"0\"",
    "option3" : "Zero",
    "option4" : "Error",
    "question" : "What is the result of the follwoing?\nint a = 0;\nnew String s1 = Integer.toString(a);"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Nothing",
    "option1" : "1 2 3 4",
    "option2" : "0 1 2 3 4 5",
    "option3" : "Nothing",
    "option4" : "0 1 2 3 4",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nfor(int i = 0; i > 5; i++){\n    System.out.println(i);\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "\"b\" becomes 1",
    "option1" : "\"b\" becomes 1",
    "option2" : "Nothing, \"b\" stays as 5",
    "option3" : "\"b\" defaults to 0",
    "option4" : "Error",
    "question" : "What happens to \"b\" following this operation.\nint a = 1, b = 5;\nb=a;"
  }, {
    "answer" : "double a = 50;",
    "option1" : "double a = 5.0;",
    "option2" : "double a;",
    "option3" : "double a = 50;",
    "option4" : "double a = 19200158.415421;",
    "question" : "Which of these is NOT a correct way to declare a variable?"
  } ],
  "counter" : {
    "35nzS2kV7VfulTX60T6Fxa8i7AJ3" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "3WqJ7OkrdSVxVMHyhlRBJi9shEs2" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "3sxiHoZWpJg9Mo0fVnecMmAQ8HE3" : {
      "counter" : 1
    },
    "4dg2LsQKZ2cMXvzuTgVaDf0Yvp73" : {
      "counter" : 100
    },
    "5PFpZ6O1NqWcZztb3gBNKgjr5rk2" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "7GFKm5atFKe84RYZgX8sK8nt29l1" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "85Fo40jYxSZDPLpAuff5AEtQmxT2" : {
      "counter" : 10
    },
    "DTNA6ZvKrUMtsjhLSOIsHjVc4gS2" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "Ef1vIrnaZnYEs9Nii43GBYK3xl83" : {
      "counter" : 10
    },
    "EilpFdoC71c4gCtqIYQPQHTqCb32" : {
      "counter" : 10
    },
    "KVJFO8KY4TexVvY1NslwfjAncw72" : {
      "counter" : 11
    },
    "NrLiKStBONViiWJLLnWznAM4NLy1" : {
      "counter" : 10
    },
    "RlOBpSjRVtS09cMLHR72FDxuVLF2" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "TJEesLHks3QD1bh7FjdasFWh6Bh2" : {
      "counter" : 3
    },
    "TiKOf4lmHOc5XvEmT2GKN4zbSKl2" : {
      "counter" : 110
    },
    "U2Z0rdpDjwP6JzZgatxkCvQZV5H3" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "XMxqLjiXNMSCApDxcxbQQZeDBe72" : {
      "counter" : 10
    },
    "XNCQ02c0ezLGU9I8fdTUUvgs1fF3" : {
      "counter" : 20
    },
    "YdIClTgND3OTWbvclQMiWHwNvO53" : {
      "counter" : 1
    },
    "ehIDj3UJDQa43XhKAI1n8UEbU903" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "exjAQlq5bsYFxahUJ2dDpkhTyBq1" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "hamBctvnt3bSQlOpHmlnjmXj79D3" : {
      "counter" : 1
    },
    "kV3kWUQAnRf01E5l3B4lI3e1r0o1" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "lssr0h94jeMIDkVzlcTIHLuXeSL2" : {
      "counter" : 30
    },
    "mIZ6957kNxcnfRAItcJMcKJUKsA2" : {
      "counter" : 1
    },
    "tT8MYAn15aepUp6ob995LbRDTCz2" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "tsuBlt7uLbRcmOT4Ev1aj6aPV2h1" : {
      "counter" : 0
    },
    "zayHBkdv8rY1ZenlsfFfWFUoDo93" : {
      "counter" : 0
    }
  },
  "inputQuiz" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "import java.util.Scanner;",
    "option1" : "import java.util.Scanner;",
    "option2" : "import java.util.input;",
    "option3" : "import java.util.scanner;",
    "option4" : "import java.util.Input;",
    "question" : "Which of these is the correct way to get the Scanner class?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Scanner sc = new Scanner(System.in);",
    "option1" : "Scanner sc = new Scanner(Input.in);",
    "option2" : "Scanner sc =  Scanner(system.in);",
    "option3" : "Scanner sc = new Scanner(System.in);",
    "option4" : "Scanner sc = Scanner(System.in);",
    "question" : "How do we create a Scanner instance in our program?"
  }, {
    "answer" : ".nextChar()",
    "option1" : ".nextInt()",
    "option2" : ".nextChar()",
    "option3" : ".nextFloat()",
    "option4" : ".nextDouble()",
    "question" : "Which of these is NOT an input method?"
  }, {
    "answer" : ".hasNextString()",
    "option1" : ".hasNextLine()",
    "option2" : ".hasNextFloat()",
    "option3" : ".hasNextInt()",
    "option4" : ".hasNextString()",
    "question" : "Which of these is NOT a boolean input method?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "42.0",
    "option1" : "s1",
    "option2" : "42.0",
    "option3" : "42",
    "option4" : "\"42\"",
    "question" : "What is the result of the follwoing?\nString s1 = new String(\"42\");\ndouble a = Double.parseDouble(s1);"
  } ],
  "inputRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "2147483647",
    "option1" : "74812",
    "option2" : "2571398",
    "option3" : "2147483647",
    "option4" : "There is no max",
    "question" : "What is the max size of an int?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "0 1 2 3 4",
    "option1" : "1 2 3 4",
    "option2" : "0 1 2 3 4 5",
    "option3" : "jjjjj",
    "option4" : "0 1 2 3 4",
    "question" : "What type of result of the following?\nfor(int i = 0; i < 5; i++){\n    System.out.println(i + \" \");\n}\nSystem.out.println( );"
  }, {
    "answer" : "2",
    "option1" : "4",
    "option2" : "14",
    "option3" : "120",
    "option4" : "2",
    "question" : "What is the value of sum?\nint sum = 20%6;"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Error",
    "option1" : "On",
    "option2" : "Off",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "\"Off\"",
    "question" : "What is the output of the follwing\nString state = \"on\";\nif(state = \"on\"){\n    System.out.println(\"On\");\n}else{\n    System.out.println(\"Off\");\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "0",
    "option1" : "0",
    "option2" : "true",
    "option3" : "false",
    "option4" : "-3",
    "question" : "Which is the result of the following?\nString s1 = new String(\"abc\");\nString s2 = new String(\"abc\");\nSystem.out.println(s1.compareTo(s2));"
  } ],
  "iterationQuiz" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "while loop, for loop, do...while loop",
    "option1" : "count up loop, count down loop, infinite loop",
    "option2" : "infinite loop, counting loop, nested loop",
    "option3" : "while loop, for loop, do...while loop",
    "option4" : "counting loop,  sentinel-controlled loop,  and result-controlled loop",
    "question" : "What are the three general types of looping structures?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Iteration allows a program to repeat a section of code",
    "option1" : "Iteration allows a program to run away from it's problems",
    "option2" : "Iteration allows a program to execute a section of code based on a condition",
    "option3" : "Iteration assings a value to a variable",
    "option4" : "Iteration allows a program to repeat a section of code",
    "question" : "What is Iteration?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "do...while",
    "option1" : "do...while",
    "option2" : "while",
    "option3" : "if...else",
    "option4" : "for",
    "question" : "What type of loop is this?\ndo{\n    statement;\n    update;\n}while(condition);"
  }, {
    "answer" : "0 1 2 3 4",
    "option1" : "1 2 3 4",
    "option2" : "0 1 2 3 4 5",
    "option3" : "iiiii",
    "option4" : "0 1 2 3 4",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nfor(int i = 0; i < 5; i++){\n    System.out.println(i + \" \");\n}\nSystem.out.println( );"
  }, {
    "answer" : "5 4 3 2 1 0 -1 -2 -3 -4",
    "option1" : "-5 -4 -3 -2 -1 0",
    "option2" : "5 4 3 2 1 0",
    "option3" : "5 4 3 2 1 0 -1 -2 -3 -4",
    "option4" : "5 4 3 2 1 0 -1 -2 -3 -4 -5",
    "question" : "What type of result of the following?\nfor(int i = 5; i > -5; i--){\n    System.out.println(j + \" \");\n}\nSystem.out.println( );"
  } ],
  "iterationRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "a = (condition) ? true : false;",
    "option1" : "a = (condition) ? true ? false;",
    "option2" : "a = (condition) ? true : false;",
    "option3" : "a = (condition) : true ? false;",
    "option4" : "a = (condition) : true : false;",
    "question" : "What is the layout of a ternary operator?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "int a = 100;",
    "option1" : "a = 100;",
    "option2" : "int a = 100;",
    "option3" : "int a == 100;",
    "option4" : "int a = 100",
    "question" : "What do we use to assign a value to a variable?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "char a = 'a';",
    "option1" : "character = 'a';",
    "option2" : "char a = a;",
    "option3" : "char a = \"a\";",
    "option4" : "char a = 'a';",
    "question" : "Which of these is the correct way to initialise and assign a char?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "10",
    "option1" : "11",
    "option2" : "9",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "10",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nint a = 10;\nif(a == 10){\n    a++;\n}else{\n    a--;\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Reduces the value of a variable by 1",
    "option1" : "Increases the value of a variable by 1",
    "option2" : "Reduces the value of a variable by 1",
    "option3" : "Increases the value of a variable by a user given amount",
    "option4" : "Concatenates a 1 to the beginning of a variable",
    "question" : "What does decrement (--) do?"
  } ],
  "nloopQuiz" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "False",
    "option1" : "True",
    "option2" : "False",
    "option3" : "Maybe",
    "option4" : "The meaning of life",
    "question" : "In nested loops, the outer loop must be terminated before the inner loop"
  }, {
    "answer" : "A loop within a loop",
    "option1" : "A while loop withen a for loop",
    "option2" : "A loop on its own",
    "option3" : "A loop followed by another loop",
    "option4" : "A loop within a loop",
    "question" : "What is a nested loop?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "00001111",
    "option1" : "00001111",
    "option2" : "01",
    "option3" : "0101010101",
    "option4" : "0001111",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nfor(int i = 0; i < 2; i++){\n    for(int j = 0; j <= 3; j++){\n        System.out.println(i);\n    }\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "6",
    "option1" : "3",
    "option2" : "6",
    "option3" : "1",
    "option4" : "9",
    "question" : "How many times does the nested loop run?\nfor(int i = 1; i <= 3; i++){\n    for(int j = 1; j <= i; j++){\n    }\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "One fewer time than the main loop",
    "option1" : "Forever",
    "option2" : "One fewer time than the main loop",
    "option3" : "Each time the main loop is run",
    "option4" : "One more time than the main loop",
    "question" : "How often is the inner loop of a nested loop run?"
  } ],
  "nloopRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "String s = new String \"The Bare Minimum\";",
    "option1" : "String s = new String(\"The Bare Minimum\");",
    "option2" : "String s = new String \"The Bare Minimum\";",
    "option3" : "String s = \"The Bare Minimum\";",
    "option4" : "String s; s = \"The Bare Minimum\";",
    "question" : "Which of these is NOT how you initialize a String?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "String[] Cars = new String[5];",
    "option1" : "String[] Cars = new String[5];",
    "option2" : "String Cars = new String[5];",
    "option3" : "String[] Cars = new String[];",
    "option4" : "String[5] Cars = new String[];",
    "question" : "How do we create an array of 5 strings called Cars?"
  }, {
    "answer" : ".nextChar()",
    "option1" : ".nextInt()",
    "option2" : ".nextChar()",
    "option3" : ".nextFloat()",
    "option4" : ".nextDouble()",
    "question" : "Which of these is NOT an input method?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "true",
    "option1" : "true",
    "option2" : "false",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "None of the above",
    "question" : "What is the output of the following?\nint a = 14; b= 4;\nboolean x = (a>b)?true:false;"
  }, {
    "answer" : "5 4 3 2 1 0 -1 -2 -3 -4 -5",
    "option1" : "-5 -4 -3 -2 -1 0",
    "option2" : "5 4 3 2 1 0",
    "option3" : "5 4 3 2 1 0 -1 -2 -3 -4",
    "option4" : "5 4 3 2 1 0 -1 -2 -3 -4 -5",
    "question" : "What type of result of the following?\nfor(int i = 5; i >= -5; i--){\n    System.out.println(j + \" \");\n}\nSystem.out.println( );"
  } ],
  "opQuiz" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "Nothing, \"b\" stays as 5",
    "option1" : "\"b\" becomes 1",
    "option2" : "Nothing, \"b\" stays as 5",
    "option3" : "\"b\" defaults to 0",
    "option4" : "Error",
    "question" : "What happens to \"b\" following this operation.\nint a = 1, b = 5;\na=b;"
  }, {
    "answer" : "They are used to perform operations on variables and values.",
    "option1" : "They multiply two variables together.",
    "option2" : "They save 100s of lives a day",
    "option3" : "They are used to perform operations on variables and values.",
    "option4" : "It returns the remainder from a division.",
    "question" : "What is an operator?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "2",
    "option1" : "4",
    "option2" : "14",
    "option3" : "120",
    "option4" : "2",
    "question" : "What is the value of sum?\nint sum = 20%6;"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Increases the value of a variable by 1",
    "option1" : "Increases the value of a variable by 1",
    "option2" : "Reduces the value of a variable by 1",
    "option3" : "Increases the value of a variable by a user given amount",
    "option4" : "Concatenates a 1 to the beginning of a variable",
    "question" : "What does increment (++) do?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Error",
    "option1" : "15",
    "option2" : "50",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "5",
    "question" : "What is the result of the follwoing code?\nint x = 10;\nx *= 5"
  } ],
  "opRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "float fish = 19.7;",
    "option1" : "float fish = 19.7;",
    "option2" : "int a = 10, b = 20;",
    "option3" : "char a = 'a';",
    "option4" : "double dash = 20.0;",
    "question" : "Which one of the following declarations is NOT correct?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "19hats",
    "option1" : "iceCream",
    "option2" : "Maynooth",
    "option3" : "19hats",
    "option4" : "real_Mouse",
    "question" : "Which one of the following is NOT a correct variable name?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Error",
    "option1" : "b",
    "option2" : "\"99\"",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "99",
    "question" : "What does the following program output?\nint b = 99;\nSystem.out.println(\"b\")"
  } ],
  "ssQuiz" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "It allows a program to test several conditions and execute instructions based on their outcome",
    "option1" : "Its makes your program more efficient and reduces runtime errors.",
    "option2" : "It allows a program to test several conditions and execute instructions based on your favorite colour M&M",
    "option3" : "It allows a program to test several conditions and execute instructions based on their outcome",
    "option4" : "It allows a program to test several conditions and execute instructions based on the number of selection statements",
    "question" : "What is a Selection Statement?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "2",
    "option1" : "1",
    "option2" : "2",
    "option3" : "3",
    "option4" : "4",
    "question" : "How many choices are possible when using a single if-else statement?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "11",
    "option1" : "11",
    "option2" : "9",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "10",
    "question" : "What is the result of the following?\nint a = 10;\nif(a == 10){\n    a++;\n}else{\n    a--;\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "It allows us to check multiple conditions",
    "option1" : "It is easier to use than a single if statement",
    "option2" : "It allows us to check multiple conditions",
    "option3" : "We can check one condition at a time",
    "option4" : "7",
    "question" : "Why do we use an if...else statement?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Equal to (==) is used to compare two values equal to each other. Equal (=) is used for assigning",
    "option1" : "There is no difference",
    "option2" : "Equal to (==) is used for assigning. Equal (=) is used to compare two values equal to each other",
    "option3" : "They allow users to compare and assign values at the same time when used together",
    "option4" : "Equal to (==) is used to compare two values equal to each other. Equal (=) is used for assigning",
    "question" : "What is the difference between equal (=) and equal to (==)?"
  } ],
  "ssRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "999",
    "option1" : "1001",
    "option2" : "-1000",
    "option3" : "999",
    "option4" : "1000",
    "question" : "What is the result of the follwing?\n1000--;"
  }, {
    "answer" : "0.0f",
    "option1" : "0",
    "option2" : "0.0",
    "option3" : "f",
    "option4" : "0.0f",
    "question" : "The default value of a static float variable in Java is"
  }, {
    "answer" : "triple",
    "option1" : "double",
    "option2" : "char",
    "option3" : "triple",
    "option4" : "int",
    "question" : "Which of these are not a Variable?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "3",
    "option1" : "4",
    "option2" : "3.333",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "3",
    "question" : "What is the value of sum?\nint sum = 20/6;"
  }, {
    "answer" : "All the above",
    "option1" : "It may destroy your learning",
    "option2" : "It will get you in trouble",
    "option3" : "Plagiarism is unethical",
    "option4" : "All the above",
    "question" : "Why is plagiarism bad?"
  } ],
  "stringsQuiz" : [ null, {
    "answer" : ".length()",
    "option1" : ".length",
    "option2" : ".size()",
    "option3" : ".length()",
    "option4" : ".Lenth()",
    "question" : "How do we find the length of a String?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "String s = new String \"Hello, World\";",
    "option1" : "String s = new String(\"Hello, World\");",
    "option2" : "String s = new String \"Hello, World\";",
    "option3" : "String s = \"Hello, World\";",
    "option4" : "String s; s = \"Hello World\";",
    "question" : "Which of these is NOT how you initialize a String?"
  }, {
    "answer" : ".subString()",
    "option1" : ".toUpperCase()",
    "option2" : ".charAt()",
    "option3" : ".subString()",
    "option4" : ".indexOf()",
    "question" : "Which of these is NOT a valid String method?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Hell#, W#rld",
    "option1" : "Hell#, World",
    "option2" : "Hell#, W#rld",
    "option3" : "Hello, W#rld",
    "option4" : "Hello, World",
    "question" : "Which is the result of the following?\nString s1 = new String(\"Hello, World\");\nString s2 = s1.replace('o','#');\nSystem.out.print(s2);"
  }, {
    "answer" : "-3",
    "option1" : "0",
    "option2" : "true",
    "option3" : "false",
    "option4" : "-3",
    "question" : "Which is the result of the following?\nString s1 = new String(\"abc\");\nString s2 = new String(\"def\");\nSystem.out.println(s1.compareTo(s2));"
  } ],
  "stringsRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "123",
    "option1" : "123",
    "option2" : "0123",
    "option3" : "012",
    "option4" : "12",
    "question" : "What is the output of the following?\nint p = 0;\nwhile(p < 3){\n    p++;\n    System.out.print(p);\n}"
  }, {
    "answer" : "Block",
    "option1" : "Branch",
    "option2" : "Brick",
    "option3" : "Blob",
    "option4" : "Block",
    "question" : "A sequence of statements contained within a pair of braces (\"{\" and \"}\") is called a?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "++",
    "option1" : "-",
    "option2" : "++",
    "option3" : "--",
    "option4" : "+",
    "question" : "__________ operator increases the value of the operand by 1."
  }, {
    "answer" : "7",
    "option1" : "9",
    "option2" : "8",
    "option3" : "10",
    "option4" : "7",
    "question" : "What is the value of the following expression?\n(2 - 6) / 2 + 9"
  }, {
    "answer" : "1 3 5 7 9",
    "option1" : "1 3 5 7 9",
    "option2" : "1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9",
    "option3" : "1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10",
    "option4" : "13579",
    "question" : "What is the output of the following?\nfor(int i = 1; i <= 10; i++){\n    System.out.println(i + \" \");\n    i++;\n}"
  } ],
  "varQuestions" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "32",
    "option1" : "4",
    "option2" : "8",
    "option3" : "16",
    "option4" : "32",
    "question" : "How much space in memory (in bits) does an int occupy?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "String",
    "option1" : "char",
    "option2" : "int",
    "option3" : "String",
    "option4" : "boolean",
    "question" : "Which of these is NOT a primitive type"
  }, {
    "answer" : "I am 20years old",
    "option1" : "I am 99 years old",
    "option2" : "I am 20years old",
    "option3" : "Error",
    "option4" : "I am 20 years old",
    "question" : "What is the output of the following code?\nint a = 20, b = 99;\nSystem.out.println(\"I am \" + a + \"years old\");"
  }, {
    "answer" : "a = 9;",
    "option1" : "int a = 5;",
    "option2" : "int a;",
    "option3" : "int a, b;",
    "option4" : "a = 9;",
    "question" : "Which of these is NOT a correct way to declare a variable?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "It is used to store a value or data type",
    "option1" : "It is used to solve computer problems",
    "option2" : "A type of cryptocurrency",
    "option3" : "It is used to store numbers",
    "option4" : "It is used to store a value or data type",
    "question" : "What is a Variable?"
  } ],
  "varRev" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "System.out.print",
    "option1" : "System.out.println",
    "option2" : "System.out.print",
    "option3" : "system.out.print",
    "option4" : "System.out.printLn",
    "question" : "In order to print and not go to a new line we do..."
  }, {
    "answer" : ";",
    "option1" : ";",
    "option2" : ".",
    "option3" : "Nothing",
    "option4" : ":",
    "question" : "Whast must we out at the end of every statement in Java?"
  } ],
  "wipQuestions" : [ null, {
    "answer" : "A detailed step of instructions",
    "option1" : "A detailed step of instructions",
    "option2" : "Something I made up on the go",
    "option3" : "Kevin",
    "option4" : "A way to get an easy pass",
    "question" : "What is an Algorithm?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "System.out.println(\"Hello, World\");",
    "option1" : "System.out.println(\"Hello, World\")",
    "option2" : "print(\"Hello, World\");",
    "option3" : "Hello, World;",
    "option4" : "System.out.println(\"Hello, World\");",
    "question" : "How can we print \"Hello, World\" to the screen?"
  }, {
    "answer" : "No",
    "option1" : "Yes",
    "option2" : "No",
    "option3" : "Only on bank holidays",
    "option4" : "What is code?",
    "question" : "Should you copy someone else's code for assignments?"
  } ]
}
